<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Assembly Esthetician</title>
    <link>/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Assembly Esthetician</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 30 May 2020 17:44:36 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Cyber Eyepatch I</title>
      <link>/posts/002-eyepatch/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 May 2020 17:44:36 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/002-eyepatch/</guid>
      <description>Yo ho, yo ho, a pirate&amp;rsquo;s life for me. Unfortunately my right eye does not work all that well, normally it does not look all that different than my left, but it rarely properly lines up with it to allow me to see 3d objects like most people. One project that has been on my to do list for a while now has been creating a cool, cyborg esque eye-patch for that eye.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hy for Fun and Profit</title>
      <link>/posts/001-hy-for-fun-and-profit/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 May 2020 17:00:52 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/001-hy-for-fun-and-profit/</guid>
      <description>Well maybe not profit… Python is a language famous for being so similar to natural languages that it appears to be almost the same as pseudocode. This has resulted in it becoming tremendously popular and given it a massive ecosystem of different libraries that allow you to do all sorts of interesting things: from scientific computing to cluster automation Python does everything. Python also serves as a good language for beginners and thus, unfortunately, is often looked down on for not being a sufficiently 1337 programming language.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Programmatic Beauty I</title>
      <link>/posts/000-programmatic-beauty-i/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Dec 2019 17:00:52 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/000-programmatic-beauty-i/</guid>
      <description>Assembly, Lisp, and Turing Machines, oh my! I am sometimes overwhelmed by the sheer beauty of a concept in computer science to such a degree that I am moved to tears at points. To be totally honest it is probably this reaction to the beauty of computer science that makes me love learning more than any sort of pretense of productivity (though that matters too).
In the interest of sharing the things I love with others I have created this little overview of the subjects that I find most beautiful and profound in computer science.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>